Now that we have an unrolled example of input
现在我们已经查看了该网络的
and output of the network, let's go another level deeper,
输入和输出展开示例 我们再深入一层
and look at some of the parameters of the model.
看看该模型的一些参数
So at this point of the course you
学到本课程的这一阶段后
know that you can't just feed words directly to the network.
你已经知道我们不能直接向网络提供单词
We need to turn the words into vectors first.
我们首先需要将单词转换为向量
This is the same concept we saw in word2vec
这和我们在 word2vec
and the sentiment analysis RNN lessons.
及情感分析 RNN 课程中见到的概念是一样的
Our first set of parameters are the ways
第一组参数是
that we multiply the input vectors
我们用来与输入相乘的权重
by every time we take an element.
每次传入一个元素
Now here's the thing.
澄清下
So you don't have to worry about this as much.
你不需要太担心这一步
So Tensorflow actually shields you from a lot of this,
Tensorflow 已经在后台帮你处理
and then takes care of a lot of these different parts for you.
它会帮助你实施很多部分
So don't worry about implementation for now.
所以暂时不用担心如何实现
Just make sure you're comfortable
只需大概了解下
with the general concept.
基本概念就行
And then we'll get to implementation later.
稍后我们将介绍如何实现
But this is one of the things that Tensorflow handles for us.
实际上 Tensorflow 会帮助我们实现的
But it's good nonetheless to understand.
但了解下理论知识还是有帮助的
So we have U, which is the input matrix of weights
这里的 U 表示与输入相乘的
that we multiply the inputs with.
权重矩阵
And then we have A, which we multiply the hidden state
这里是与编码器阶输出的值相乘的A 矩阵
as it travels between time steps of the encoder,
每个时间步长都会有和A矩阵
and also out to the decoder.
和编码器输出的值相乘并最后输出到解码器中
We also have another matrix of weights called V
然后是另一个权重矩阵 叫做 V
that we multiply the hidden state when the decoder outputs
当解码器输出隐藏状态的值时
its values, and another one called
我们用V与之相乘
B that goes that's multiplied by the hidden state when
另一个是 B 它处于解码器时间步长之间
it travels between decoder time stamps.
传播时会与隐藏状态相乘
The last major component of such a model
此类模型的最后一个重要组件是
is a fully connected layer at the output
在输出端的完全连接层
to translate the state of the network
负责将网络状态
into an output we can choose.
转换为我们可以选择的输出
So these would be the output logits.
这些将是输出值
The number of these logits is the same
这些输出值的数量
as the size of our vocabulary.
与我们的词汇大小相同
The logit with the highest value corresponds to the word
包含最大值的输出值的的对应的是
that the model wants to output.
模型想要输出的单词
So we'll take an example.
我们看个示例
We'll clarify a little bit.
详细了解下
So let's look at this simple vocabulary.
我们看看这个简单的词汇表
So if we only have that one example of input and output,
假设只有一个输入和输出示例
how are you, I am good, we will have a vocabulary of size 11.
How are you? I am good 词汇大小是 11
Never mind the first four.
前四个别管
So these are set.
这些是设定好的
These will be useful later.
稍后将用到
So we reserve the first four spots
我们将词汇表中的前四个
in the vocabulary for PAD, for EOS, which is in the sentence.
保留为 PAD EOS（表示句子结束）
UNK is unknown, and then we also have GO.
UNK（表示未知）然后是 GO
So we've seen GO in some of these.
我们已经见过 GO
But we'll get to that later in the implementation stage.
我们稍后在实现阶段将详细介绍
And then we have the list of our words
然后是训练数据中
that we actually use in our training data.
实际用到的单词列表
So this is our vocabulary.
这就是我们的词汇表
It has 11 elements.
有 11 个元素
And so at each time step of the decoder,
在解码器的每个时间步长
the output of this network will tell us
该网络的输出将根据训练数据
which element is most likely to be generated,
告诉我们哪个元素
based on the training data.
最有可能被生成
So this is a small example, so we have a small vocabulary.
这是个很小的示例 词汇表很小
In real data sets, you'll outcome
在实际操作中
across vocabularies of tens of thousands usually of examples.
你会遇到有数千个示例的词汇表
So you'll have tens of thousands of logits in that last layer
所以网络的最后一个层级
of the network.
将有数千个输出值
So luckily, this is probably the last time
幸运的是 这可能是
you'll have to look at this view of the network.
你最后一次需要查看该网络的这一结构
Tensorflow defines an API for sequence
Tensorflow 定义了一个序列到序列 API
to sequence that hides away a lot of these details.
将很多这种细节都隐藏起来了
And you just have to use its API to define how
你只需使用该 API 来定义
you want the network to work.
你希望网络如何工作